Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65
- The Garment Worker, 1922-1923 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.41 (1923: Aug. 3)
  - Item 42: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.42 (1923: Aug. 10)
  - Item 43: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.43 (1923: Aug. 17)
  - Item 44: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.44 (1923: Aug. 24)
  - Item 45: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.45 (1923: Aug. 31)
  - Item 46: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.46 (1923: Sept. 7)
  - Item 47: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.47 (1923: Sept. 14)
  - Item 48: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.48 (1923: Sept. 21)
  - Item 49: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.49 (1923: Sept. 28)
  - Item 50: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.50 (1923: Oct. 5)
  - Item 51: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.51 (1923: Oct. 12)
  - Item 52: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.52 (1923: Oct. 19)
- The Garment Worker, 1923-1924 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.1 (1923: Oct. 26)
  - Item 2: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.2 (1923: Nov. 2)
  - Item 3: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.3 (1923: Nov. 9)
  - Item 4: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.4 (1923: Nov. 16)
  - Item 5: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.5 (1923: Nov. 23)
  - Item 6: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.6 (1923: Nov. 30)
  - Item 7: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.7 (1923: Dec. 7)
  - Item 8: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.8 (1923: Dec. 14)
  - Item 9: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.9 (1923: Dec. 21)
  - Item 10: The Garment Worker, 1923; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.10 (1923: Dec. 28)
  - Item 11: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.11 (1924: Jan. 4)
  - Item 12: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.12 (1924: Jan. 11)
  - Item 13: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.13 (1924: Jan. 18)
  - Item 14: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.14 (1924: Jan. 25)
  - Item 15: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.15 (1924: Feb. 1)
  - Item 16: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.16 (1924: Feb. 8)
  - Item 17: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.17 (1924: Feb. 15)
  - Item 18: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.18 (1924: Feb. 22)
  - Item 19: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.19 (1924: Feb. 29)
  - Item 20: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.20 (1924: Mar. 7)
  - Item 21: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.21 (1924: Mar. 14)
  - Item 22: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.22 (1924: Mar. 21)
  - Item 23: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.23 (1924: Mar. 28)
  - Item 24: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.25 (1924: Apr. 11)
  - Item 25: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.26 (1924: Apr. 18)
  - Item 26: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.27 (1924: Apr. 25)
  - Item 27: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.28 (1924: May 2)
  - Item 28: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.29 (1924: May 9)
  - Item 29: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.30 (1924: May 16)
  - Item 30: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.31 (1924: May 23)
  - Item 31: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.32 (1924: May 30)
  - Item 32: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.33 (1924: June 6)
  - Item 33: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.34 (1924: June 13)
  - Item 34: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.35 (1924: June 20)
  - Item 35: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.36 (1924: June 27)
  - Item 36: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.37 (1924: July 4)
  - Item 37: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.38 (1924: July 11)
  - Item 38: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.39 (1924: July 18)
  - Item 39: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.40 (1924: July 25)
  - Item 40: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.41 (1924: Aug. 1)
  - Item 41: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.42 (1924: Aug. 8)
  - Item 42: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.43 (1924: Aug. 15)
  - Item 43: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.44 (1924: Aug. 22)
  - Item 44: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.45 (1924: Aug. 29)
  - Item 45: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.46 (1924: Sept. 5)
  - Item 46: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.47 (1924: Sept. 12)
  - Item 47: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.48 (1924: Sept. 19)
  - Item 48: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.49 (1924: Sept. 26)
  - Item 49: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.50 (1924: Oct. 3)
  - Item 50: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.51 (1924: Oct. 10)
  - Item 51: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.52 (1924: Oct. 17)
- The Garment Worker, 1924-1925 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.1 (1924: Oct. 24)
  - Item 2: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.2 (1924: Oct. 31)
  - Item 3: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.3 (1924: Nov. 7)
  - Item 4: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.4 (1924: Nov. 14)
  - Item 5: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.5 (1924: Nov. 21)
  - Item 6: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.6 (1924: Nov. 28)
  - Item 7: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.7 (1924: Dec. 5)
  - Item 8: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.8 (1924: Dec. 12)
  - Item 9: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.9 (1924: Dec. 19)
  - Item 10: The Garment Worker, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.10 (1924: Dec. 26)
  - Item 11: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.11 (1925: Jan. 2)
  - Item 12: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.12 (1925: Jan. 9)
  - Item 13: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.13 (1925: Jan. 16)
  - Item 14: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.14 (1925: Jan. 23)
  - Item 15: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.15 (1925: Jan. 30)
  - Item 16: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.16 (1925: Feb. 6)
  - Item 17: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.17 (1925: Feb. 13)
  - Item 18: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.18 (1925: Feb. 20)
  - Item 19: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.19 (1925: Feb. 27)
  - Item 20: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.20 (1925: Mar. 6)
  - Item 21: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.21 (1925: Mar. 13)
  - Item 22: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.22 (1925: Mar. 20)
  - Item 23: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.23 (1925: Mar. 27)
  - Item 24: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.24 (1925: Apr. 3)
  - Item 25: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.25 (1925: Apr. 10)
  - Item 26: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.26 (1925: Apr. 17)
  - Item 27: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.27 (1925: Apr. 24)
  - Item 28: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.28 (1925: May 1)
  - Item 29: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.29 (1925: May 8)
  - Item 30: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.30 (1925: May 15)
  - Item 31: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.31 (1925: May 22)
  - Item 32: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.32 (1925: May 29)
  - Item 33: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.33 (1925: June 5)
  - Item 34: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.34 (1925: June 12)
  - Item 35: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.35 (1925: June 19)
  - Item 36: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.36 (1925: June 26)
  - Item 37: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.37 (1925: July 3)
  - Item 38: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.38 (1925: July 10)
  - Item 39: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.39 (1925: July 17)
  - Item 40: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.40 (1925: July 24)
  - Item 41: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.41 (1925: July 31)
  - Item 42: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.42 (1925: Aug. 7)
  - Item 43: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.43 (1925: Aug. 14)
  - Item 44: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.44 (1925: Aug. 21)
  - Item 45: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.45 (1925: Aug. 28)
  - Item 46: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.46 (1925: Sept. 4)
  - Item 47: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.47 (1925: Sept. 11)
  - Item 48: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.48 (1925: Sept. 18)
  - Item 49: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.49 (1925: Sept. 25)
  - Item 50: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.50 (1925: Oct. 2)
  - Item 51: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.51 (1925: Oct. 9)
  - Item 52: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.52 (1925: Oct. 16)
- The Garment Worker, 1925-1926 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.1 (1925: Oct. 23)
  - Item 2: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.2 (1925: Oct. 30)
  - Item 3: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.3 (1925: Nov. 6)
  - Item 4: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.4 (1925: Nov. 13)
  - Item 5: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.5 (1925: Nov. 20)
  - Item 6: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.6 (1925: Nov. 27)
  - Item 7: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.7 (1925: Dec. 4)
  - Item 8: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.8 (1925: Dec. 11)
  - Item 9: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.9 (1925: Dec. 18)
  - Item 10: The Garment Worker, 1925; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.10 (1925: Dec. 25)
  - Item 11: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.11 (1926: Jan. 1)
  - Item 12: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.12 (1926: Jan. 8)
  - Item 13: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.13 (1926: Jan. 15)
  - Item 14: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.14 (1926: Jan. 22)
  - Item 15: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.15 (1926: Jan. 29)
  - Item 16: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.16 (1926: Feb. 5)
  - Item 17: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.17 (1926: Feb. 12)
  - Item 18: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.18 (1926: Feb. 19)
  - Item 19: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.19 (1926: Feb. 26)
  - Item 20: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.20 (1926: Mar. 5)
  - Item 21: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.21 (1926: Mar. 12)
  - Item 22: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.22 (1926: Mar. 19)
  - Item 23: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.23 (1926: Mar. 26)
  - Item 24: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.24 (1926: Apr. 2)
  - Item 25: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.25 (1926: Apr. 9)
  - Item 26: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.26 (1926: Apr. 16)
  - Item 27: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.27 (1926: Apr. 23)
  - Item 28: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.28 (1926: Apr. 30)
  - Item 29: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.29 (1926: May 7)
  - Item 30: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.30 (1926: May 14)
  - Item 31: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.31 (1926: May 21)
  - Item 32: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.32 (1926: May 28)
  - Item 33: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.33 (1926: June 4)
  - Item 34: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.34 (1926: June 11)
  - Item 35: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.35 (1926: June 18)
  - Item 36: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.36 (1926: June 25)
  - Item 37: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.37 (1926: July 2)
  - Item 38: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.38 (1926: July 9)
  - Item 39: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.39 (1926: July 16)
  - Item 40: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.40 (1926: July 23)
  - Item 41: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.41 (1926: July 30)
  - Item 42: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.42 (1926: Aug. 6)
  - Item 43: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.43 (1926: Aug. 13)
  - Item 44: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.44 (1926: Aug. 20)
  - Item 45: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.45 (1926: Aug. 27)
  - Item 46: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.46 (1926: Sept. 3)
  - Item 47: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.47 (1926: Sept. 10)
  - Item 48: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.48 (1926: Sept. 17)
  - Item 49: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.49 (1926: Sept. 24)
  - Item 50: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.50 (1926: Oct. 1)
  - Item 51: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.51 (1926: Oct. 8)
  - Item 52: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.52 (1926: Oct. 15)
- The Garment Worker, 1926-1927 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.1 (1926: Oct. 22)
  - Item 2: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.2 (1926: Oct. 29)
  - Item 3: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.3 (1926: Nov. 5)
  - Item 4: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.4 (1926: Nov. 12)
  - Item 5: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.5 (1926: Nov. 19)
  - Item 6: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.6 (1926: Nov. 26)
  - Item 7: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.7 (1926: Dec. 3)
  - Item 8: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.8 (1926: Dec. 10)
  - Item 9: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.9 (1926: Dec. 17)
  - Item 10: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.10 (1926: Dec. 24)
  - Item 11: The Garment Worker, 1926; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.11 (1926: Dec. 31)
  - Item 12: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.12 (1927: Jan. 7)
  - Item 13: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.13 (1927: Jan. 14)
  - Item 14: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.14 (1927: Jan. 21)
  - Item 15: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.15 (1927: Jan. 28)
  - Item 16: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.16 (1927: Feb. 4)
  - Item 17: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.17 (1927: Feb. 11)
  - Item 18: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.18 (1927: Feb. 18)
  - Item 19: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.19 (1927: Feb. 25)
  - Item 20: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.20 (1927: Mar. 4)
  - Item 21: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.21 (1927: Mar. 11)
  - Item 22: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.22 (1927: Mar. 18)
  - Item 23: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.23 (1927: Mar. 25)
  - Item 24: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.24 (1927: Apr. 1)
  - Item 25: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.25 (1927: Apr. 8)
  - Item 26: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.26 (1927: Apr. 15)
  - Item 27: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.27 (1927: Apr. 22)
  - Item 28: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.28 (1927: Apr. 29)
  - Item 29: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.29 (1927: May 6)
  - Item 30: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.30 (1927: May 13)
  - Item 31: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.31 (1927: May 20)
  - Item 32: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.32 (1927: May 27)
  - Item 33: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.33 (1927: June 3)
  - Item 34: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.34 (1927: June 10)
  - Item 35: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.35 (1927: June 17)
  - Item 36: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.36 (1927: June 24)
  - Item 37: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.37 (1927: July 1)
  - Item 38: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.38 (1927: July 8)
  - Item 39: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.39 (1927: July 15)
  - Item 40: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.40 (1927: July 22)
  - Item 41: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.41 (1927: July 29)
  - Item 42: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.42 (1927: Aug. 5)
  - Item 43: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.43 (1927: Aug. 12)
  - Item 44: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.44 (1927: Aug. 19)
  - Item 45: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.45 (1927: Aug. 26)
  - Item 46: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.46 (1927: Sept. 2)
  - Item 47: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.47 (1927: Sept. 9)
  - Item 48: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.48 (1927: Sept. 16)
  - Item 49: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.49 (1927: Sept. 23)
  - Item 50: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.50 (1927: Sept. 30)
  - Item 51: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.51 (1927: Oct. 7)
  - Item 52: The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.52 (1927: Oct. 14)
- The Garment Worker, 1927; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)